Planned Parenthood Federation of America Records (PPFA II): SERIES V. Affiliates, 1930-80 (Part 1)
Sophia Smith Collection
Planned Parenthood Federation of America Records (PPFA II): SERIES V. Affiliates (Part 1)
1921, 1939-1981
Planned Parenthood Federation of America
371a_s5_p1
65 linear feet
Sophia Smith Collection Smith College Northampton, MA
This series contains the national office's records on affiliate activities and includes minutes, affiliation materials, copies of correspondence, clippings, publicity, reports, and financial material.This Series forms part of the PPFA II Records
This Series forms part of the PPFA II Records
This series contains the national office's records on affiliate activities and includes minutes, affiliation materials, copies of correspondence, clippings, publicity, reports, and financial material.
The bulk of the material is arranged alphabetically by state. The first set of state material is local affiliates' minutes. This is followed by minutes and meeting material from regional offices; it is unclear whether this duplicates material contained in SERIES VI. REGIONS. Next comes general administrative material, which includes files on services offered by affiliates, including birth control methods and sexually transmitted disease education. The remainder of material, the bulk of this series, is from affiliate offices and filed by state. General state programs such as anti-poverty and migrant worker programs are filed first within a state, and then local and metropolitan affiliates are listed. Files include affiliate reports, statistics, publicity, and correspondence. There are some inconsistencies: New York City comes before New York State, but there is also New York City material within New York State and some at the end of the series. The state of Connecticut is filed last. It contains a significant amount of information regarding Griswold vs. Connecticut and the fight to disseminate birth control and contraceptive information. The New York State files contain some material pertaining to the relaxation of abortion laws in the early 1970s. The end of the series includes miscellany and histories of the regions.
NOTE: To view the series descriptions and contents lists, click on the series links below. Some files are quite large and may take several minutes to load, depending on your internet connection.
Due to it's large size, the SERIES V container list is divided into two parts: Part 1 and Part 2.
This collection is organized into ten series:
I. Chronological Files
II. Classified Files
Part 1
Part 2
III. Publications
IV. Subject Files
V. Affiliates
Part 1
Part 2
VI. Regions
VII. Minutes
VIII. Foreign
IX. Guttmacher
[X. Restricted]
PPFA has closed records created January 1, 1985 or later, with the exception of many published materials which are open to research. All records having to do with clinic defense and security are closed. PPFA has closed a small section of files in box 206 for fifty years. Researchers may request access to restricted materials from PPFA.
The Margaret Sanger Papers Microfilm Edition: Smith College Collection Series, edited by Esther Katz, et al., University Publications of America, 1995
Periodic additions to the collection are expected.
PPFA deposited these records in 1988. Various departments have since sent miscellaneous additions.
Best, Winfield; Guttmacher, Alan Frank, 1898-; McCormick, Katherine Dexter, 1876-1967; Rose, D. Kenneth; Sanger, Margaret, 1879-1966; Wattleton, Faye; Alan Guttmacher Institute--History; American Birth Control League--History; Abortion--Law and legislation-United States--History--Sources; Abortion services--History--Sources; Birth Control Clinical Research Bureau (New York, N.Y.)--History; Birth Control Federation of America--History; International Planned Parenthood Federation--History; Planned Parenthood Federation of America--History; Planned Parenthood-World Population (U.S.)--History; Birth control clinics--United States--History--Sources; Birth control--History--20th century--Sources; Birth control--Developing countries--History--20th century--Sources; Contraceptives--Research--History; Hygiene, Sexual--History--20th century; Human reproduction--Political aspects; Population policy--History--20th century; Reproductive health--Statistics; Sex instruction--History; Women--Health and hygiene--United States--20th century; Women's health services--United States--20th century
This Series forms part of the PPFA II Records
See also the PPFA I Records.
Related material can be found in the Margaret Sanger Papers, Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College, and at the Library of Congess.
- SERIES V. AFFILIATES (PART 1)
  - Minutes
    - Alabama
      - Birmingham
        - 1963-1974 (Box 134, Folder 1)
        - 1975-77 (Box 134)
      - Huntsville
        - 1970 (Box 134, Folder 2)
        - 1975-77 (Box 134)
      - Tuscaloosa, 1972 (Box 134, Folder 3)
    - Alaska, Anchorage, Anchorage PP League
      - 1970 (Box 134, Folder 4)
      - 1976-77 (Box 134)
    - Arizona
      - Phoenix
        - 1964-1973 (Box 134, Folder 5)
        - 1976 (Box 134)
      - Tucson, 1965-70 (Box 134, Folder 6)
    - California
      - Bakersfield, 1965-1966 (Box 134, Folder 7)
      - Contra Costa, PP from 1962, 1962-1971 (Box 134, Folder 8)
      - Claremont, PP Pomona Valley, 1965 (Box 134, Folder 9)
      - Davis, PP Association of Yolo County (formerly Woodland), 1977 (Box 134, Folder 10)
      - Fresno, PP of Fresno, 1975-1977 (Box 134, Folder 11)
      - Los Angeles, Area Council, 1965 (Box 134, Folder 12)
      - Los Angeles
        - 1964-1969 (Box 134, Folder 13)
        - 1977 (Box 134, Folder 14)
      - Oakland, 1965-1967 (Box 134, Folder 14)
      - Pacific Grove, PP of Monterey County, 1975-1978 (Box 134, Folder 15)
      - Pasadena
        - 1964-1966 (Box 134, Folder 16)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 134)
      - San Bernadino, PP Council, 1966 (Box 134, Folder 17)
      - San Diego, PP from 1963
        - 1963-1970 (Box 134, Folder 18)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 134)
      - San Francisco, 1964-1967 (Box 134, Folder 19)
      - San Francisco, PP Alameda/San Francisco
        - 1970 (Box 134, Folder 20)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 134)
      - San Jose, PP Association of Santa Clara County
        - 1965-1971 (Box 134, Folder 21)
        - 1975-1977 (Box 134)
      - San Mateo, 1977 (Box 134, Folder 22)
      - San Raphael, PP Association of Marin County
        - 1965 (Box 134, Folder 23)
        - 1975 (Box 134)
      - Santa Ana, PP Association of Orange County
        - 1965-1971 (Box 134, Folder 24)
        - 1976-77 (Box 134)
      - Santa Barbara, PP Parenthood Committee from 1964
        - 1965-1974 (Box 134, Folder 25)
        - 1975-77 (Box 134)
      - Santa Cruz, PP of Santa Cruz
        - 1971 (Box 134, Folder 26)
        - 1976 (Box 134)
      - Stockton, PP of Joaquin County, 1976-1977 (Box 134, Folder 27)
      - Whittier, PP Conference from 1958 (empty) (Box 134, Folder 28)
    - Colorado, Denver
      - 1964-1971 (Box 134, Folder 29)
      - 1975-77 (Box 134)
    - Connecticut
      - Greater New Haven, 1964-1965 (Box 134, Folder 30)
      - New Haven, 1964-1969 (Box 134, Folder 31)
    - Delaware, Wilmington
      - 1965-1974 (Box 134, Folder 32)
      - 1976 (Box 134)
    - District of Columbia, Washington
      - 1965, 1974 (Box 134, Folder 33)
      - 1975-77 (Box 134)
    - Florida
      - Clearwater, PP Pinellas County from 1963, 1965-1970 (Box 134, Folder 34)
      - Gainsville, PP North Central Florida from 1976
        - 1974 (Box 134, Folder 35)
        - 1975-76 (Box 134)
      - Jacksonville, PP of Northeast Florida from 1967
        - 1967-1969 (Box 134, Folder 36)
        - 1975-1977 (Box 134)
      - Jacksonville, The Duval County Family Planning Project, 1971 (Box 134, Folder 37)
      - Miami, PP Association of Dade County, 1963-1965 (Box 134, Folder 38)
      - Opa Locka, PP of South Florida, Inc., 1976 (Box 134, Folder 39)
      - Orlando, PP Association of Central Florida, 1971 (Box 134, Folder 40)
      - Sarasota, PP of Southwest Florida, Inc. (formerly Sarasota County)
        - 1965-1973 (Box 134, Folder 41)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 134)
      - West Palm Beach, PP Palm Beach Area, 1975-1977 (Box 134, Folder 42)
    - Georgia
      - Atlanta
        - 1964-1971 (Box 134, Folder 43)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 134)
      - Augusta
        - 1968-1969, 1974 (Box 134, Folder 44)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 134)
    - Hawaii, Hawaii PP, Inc., 1975-1977 (Box 134, Folder 45)
    - Idaho, Boise, PP Association of Idaho, Inc., 1976 (Box 134, Folder 46)
    - Illinois
      - Carbondale, PP League, Minutes, 1956 (Box 134, Folder 47)
      - Champaign
        - 1964-1965 (Box 134, Folder 48)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 134)
      - Chicago Area
        - 1964-1969, 1974 (Box 134, Folder 49)
        - 1975, 1977 (Box 134)
      - Danville, PP Association, 1954 (Box 134, Folder 50)
      - Decatur, PP of Decatur
        - 1974 (Box 134, Folder 51)
        - 1977 (Box 134)
      - Peoria, PP Association of the Peoria Area, 1975-1978 (Box 134, Folder 52)
      - Springfield, PP Association, 1958-1963 (Box 134, Folder 53)
      - Waukegan, PP Association Lake County, 1949, 1955 (Box 134, Folder 54)
    - Indiana
      - Bloomington
        - 1964-1965 (Box 134, Folder 55)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 134)
      - Evansville
        - 1964 (Box 134, Folder 56)
        - 1977 (Box 134)
      - Gary, PP, 1964-1965, 1974 (Box 134, Folder 57)
      - Indianapolis
        - 1956 (Box 134, Folder 58)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 134)
      - Lafayette, Tecumseh Area PP Association, Inc., 1975-1977 (Box 134, Folder 59)
      - Muncie, PP of East Central Indiana, Inc., 1975-1977 (Box 134, Folder 60)
      - South Bend, PP Association from 1954
        - 1954, 1974 (Box 134, Folder 61)
        - 1975-1977 (Box 134)
      - Terra Haute, PP Association of Wabash Valley (formerly Vigo County), 1974-1975 (Box 134, Folder 62)
    - Iowa
      - Cedar Falls, PP Council, 1954-1955 (Box 134, Folder 63)
      - Cedar Rapids, PP Council, 1954-1957 (Box 134, Folder 64)
      - Des Moines, 1964-1967 (Box 134, Folder 65)
      - Mount Pleasant, PP of Southeast Iowa
        - 1973 (Box 134, Folder 66)
        - 1976 (Box 134)
      - Sioux City
        - 1964-1972 (Box 134, Folder 67)
        - 1975 (Box 134)
    - Kentucky
      - Berea, Mountain Maternal Health League from 1960
        - 1960-1965 (Box 134, Folder 68)
        - 1975 (Box 134)
      - Lexington
        - 1964-1974 (Box 134, Folder 69)
        - 1976 (Box 134)
      - Louisville, 1964-1976 (Box 134, Folder 70)
    - Maine, Bangor, Maternal Health League, 1957 (Box 134, Folder 71)
    - Regional Chesapeake Bay Area, 1964 (Box 134, Folder 72)
    - Maryland
      - Baltimore, 1964-1971 (Box 134, Folder 73)
      - Silver Springs, PP League Montgomery County, 1960 (Box 134, Folder 74)
    - Massachusetts, Boston, 1965-1969 (Box 134, Folder 75)
    - Michigan
      - Ann Arbor
        - 1964-1966 (Box 134, Folder 76)
        - 1975 (Box 134)
      - Benton Harbor, PP Association of Southwestern Michigan
        - 1973-1974 (Box 134, Folder 77)
        - 1975 (Box 134)
      - Birmingham, PP Oakland County Chapter, 1960 (Box 134, Folder 78)
      - Detroit
        - 1964-1965 (Box 134, Folder 79)
        - 1975 (Box 134)
      - Flint, PP, 1965 (Box 134, Folder 80)
      - Grand Rapids from 1964
        - 1964-1965, 1974 (Box 134, Folder 81)
        - 1976 (Box 134)
      - Kalamazoo from 1968
        - 1968-1974 (Box 134, Folder 82)
        - 1975 (Box 134)
      - Lansing, PP, 1971 (Box 134, Folder 83)
    - Minnesota
      - Minneapolis, 1964-1967 (Box 134, Folder 84)
      - St. Paul
        - 1965-1969 (Box 134, Folder 85)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 134)
    - Missouri
      - Columbia, PP of Central Missouri, 1972 (Box 134, Folder 86)
      - Kansas City, PP of Western Missouri and Kansas (formerly Greater Kansas City)
        - 1964-1974 (Box 134, Folder 87)
        - 1976 (Box 134)
      - Kerksville, PP of Northeast Missouri, 1975-1976 (Box 134, Folder 88)
      - Pemiscot County, PP Organization (Planning Committee), 1956 (Box 134, Folder 89)
      - Rolla, PP of the Central Ozarks, 1975 (Box 134, Folder 90)
      - St. Louis
        - 1964-1966 (Box 134, Folder 91)
        - 1976 (Box 134)
    - Montana
      - Billings, PP Committee, 1964-1965, 1969 (Box 134, Folder 92)
      - Missoula
        - 1972 (Box 134, Folder 93)
        - 1975 (Box 134)
    - Nebraska
      - Lincoln, 1975-1976 (Box 134, Folder 94)
      - Omaha, PP, 1965-1970 (Box 134, Folder 95)
    - New Hampshire, Lebanon, 1970 (Box 134, Folder 96)
    - New Jersey
      - Ashbury Park, PP Monmouth County, 1965-1970 (Box 134, Folder 97)
      - Bergen County, Bergen County, 1965-1971 (Box 134, Folder 98)
      - Bridgeton Area, 1964-1966 (Box 134, Folder 99)
      - Camden, 1964-1967 (Box 134, Folder 100)
      - Hackensack
        - 1974 (Box 134, Folder 101)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 134)
      - Jersey City, PP of Hudson County, 1971-1974 (Box 134, Folder 102)
      - Madison, New Jersey League Area, 1963-1965 (Box 134, Folder 103)
      - Montclair, PP Morris County, 1953 (Box 134, Folder 104)
      - Morristown, PP Morris County, 1964-1972 (Box 134, Folder 105)
      - Newark, PP Essex County, 1965-1974 (Box 134, Folder 106)
      - Paterson, PP Passaic County, 1964-1965, 1974 (Box 134, Folder 107)
      - Plainfield, 1965-1971 (Box 134, Folder 108)
      - Plainfield, PP Westfield, 1965 (Box 134, Folder 109)
      - Princeton, PP from 1960, 1960 (Box 134, Folder 110)
      - Shrewsbury, PP Monmouth County, 1974 (Box 134, Folder 111)
      - Trenton
        - 1965-1974 (Box 134, Folder 112)
        - 1975 (Box 134)
    - Nevada, Las Vegas, PP of Southern Nevada, Inc.
      - 1972 (Box 135, Folder 1)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 135)
    - New Mexico
      - Albuquerque, 1967-1974 (Box 135, Folder 2)
      - Las Cruces
        - 1965-1967 (Box 135, Folder 3)
        - 1975 (Box 135)
    - New York
      - New York City, PP Manhattan and the Bronx, 1964-1966 (Box 135, Folder 4)
      - Albany, 1965 (Box 135, Folder 5)
      - Auburn, 1964 (Box 135, Folder 6)
      - Babylon, PP South Suffolk, 1963-1965 (Box 135, Folder 7)
      - Binghamton, PP Broome County, 1964-1971 (Box 135, Folder 8)
      - Brooklyn, 1965 (Box 135, Folder 9)
      - Margaret Sanger Bureau, Board of Trustees, 1964-1969 (Box 135, Folder 10)
      - Margaret Sanger Bureau, 1965-1970 (Box 135, Folder 11)
      - Buffalo, 1965-1971 (Box 135, Folder 12)
      - Canadaigua and Ontario County, 1969 (Box 135, Folder 13)
      - Elmira, PP of Chenung County-Corning Inc. from 1970, 1970-1972 (Box 135, Folder 14)
      - Far Rockaway, 1965 (Box 135, Folder 15)
      - Geneva, PP Canandaigua and Ontario County
        - 1971 (Box 135, Folder 16)
        - 1976 (Box 135)
      - Huntington, PP North Suffolk
        - 1964-1971 (Box 135, Folder 17)
        - 1975-1977 (Box 135)
      - Jamaica, 1964-1965 (Box 135, Folder 18)
      - Kingston, PP Ulster County, 1962 (Box 135, Folder 19)
      - Mineola, PP Nassau County, 1963-1965 (Box 135, Folder 20)
      - Mt. Kisco, PP Northern Westchester, 1965-1968 (Box 135, Folder 21)
      - Mt. Vernon, PP Southern Westchester, 1964-1965 (Box 135, Folder 22)
      - Newburgh, PP Orange County, 1965-1968 (Box 135, Folder 23)
      - New Rochelle, PP, 1958 (Box 135, Folder 24)
      - New York, PP Eastern League, 1963 (Box 135, Folder 25)
      - New York City, PP of New York City, 1967 (Box 135, Folder 26)
      - Niagara Falls
        - 1964 (Box 135, Folder 27)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 135)
      - Patchogue, PP, 1965 (Box 135, Folder 28)
      - Port Chester, PP Eastern Westchester, 1965-1969 (Box 135, Folder 29)
      - Poughkeepsie, PP Dutchess County, 1964-1968 (Box 135, Folder 30)
      - Rochester, PP Monroe County, 1965-1970 (Box 135, Folder 31)
      - Schenectady, 1964-1972 (Box 135, Folder 32)
      - Syracuse, 1965 (Box 135, Folder 33)
      - Utica, 1965 (Box 135, Folder 34)
      - Watertown, PP of Northern New York and Lewis County, Chapters (Box 135)
        - 1972-1974 (Box 135, Folder 35)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 135)
      - West Nyack, PP of Rockland County, 1970 (Box 135, Folder 36)
      - White Plains, PP, 1954 (Box 135, Folder 37)
      - Yonkers, 1963-1965 (Box 135, Folder 38)
    - North Carolina
      - Ashville
        - 1968 (Box 135, Folder 39)
        - 1975 (Box 135)
      - Charlotte, 1972 (Box 135, Folder 40)
    - North Dakota, Fargo, PP, 1962-1964 (Box 135, Folder 41)
    - Ohio
      - Akron
        - 1969 (Box 135, Folder 42)
        - 1976 (Box 135)
      - Canton, 1976 (Box 135, Folder 43)
      - Cincinnati
        - 1964-1974 (Box 135, Folder 44)
        - 1975-1977 (Box 135)
      - Cleveland
        - 1965-1974 (Box 135, Folder 45)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 135)
      - Columbus
        - 1963-1971 (Box 135, Folder 46)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 135)
      - Dayton, 1953-1969 (Box 135, Folder 47)
      - Fremont, PP, 1963-1965 (Box 135, Folder 48)
      - Hamilton, 1963-1965 (Box 135, Folder 49)
      - Mansfield
        - 1968 (Box 135, Folder 50)
        - 1975 (Box 135)
      - Painesville, PP Lake County, 1959 (Box 135, Folder 51)
      - Springfield, 1963-1965 (Box 135, Folder 52)
      - Toledo
        - 1965-1970 (Box 135, Folder 53)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 135)
      - Youngstown
        - 1963-1974 (Box 135, Folder 54)
        - 1976 (Box 135)
    - Oklahoma
      - Oklahoma City
        - 1963-1967 (Box 135, Folder 55)
        - 1975 (Box 135)
      - Tulsa, 1963-1965 (Box 135, Folder 56)
    - Oregon
      - Eugene, PP Association of Lane County, 1970-1974 (Box 135, Folder 57)
      - Medford, 1976-1978 (Box 135, Folder 58)
      - Portland, PP Association, 1963-1966 (Box 135, Folder 59)
    - Pennsylvania
      - Allentown, Temporary folder, 1970-1971 (Box 135, Folder 60)
      - Bucks County, 1964-1965 (Box 135, Folder 61)
      - Easton, 1963-1965 (Box 135, Folder 62)
      - East Stoudsberg, 1963-1965 (Box 135, Folder 63)
      - Harrisburg, 1967-1969 (Box 135, Folder 64)
      - Lancaster, 1965-1972 (Box 135, Folder 65)
      - Morristown, PP Montgomery County, 1957 (Box 135, Folder 66)
      - Philadelphia, 1964-1972 (Box 135, Folder 67)
      - Pittsburgh
        - 1965-1972 (Box 135, Folder 68)
        - 1977 (Box 135)
      - Reading, 1964-1972 (Box 135, Folder 69)
      - Scranton, 1963-1972 (Box 135, Folder 70)
      - Sharon, Shenango Valley, 1963-1971 (Box 135, Folder 71)
      - West Chester, PP of Chester County, 1971-1972 (Box 135, Folder 72)
      - York
        - 1965-1970 (Box 135, Folder 73)
        - 1975 (Box 135)
      - Wilkes-Barre, 1963-1971 (Box 135, Folder 74)
    - Rhode Island, Providence, 1964-1969 (Box 135, Folder 75)
    - South Carolina
      - Beaufort (Frogmore), 1965 (Box 135, Folder 76)
      - Camden, PP Committee, 1965-1970 (Box 135, Folder 77)
      - Clearwater, PP of Aiken County, 1971 (Box 135, Folder 78)
      - Columbia, PP Committee from 1963 (Box 135, Folder 79)
    - Tennessee
      - Chattanooga, PP, 1960 (Box 136, Folder 1)
      - Knoxville
        - 1967-1972 (Box 136, Folder 2)
        - 1977 (Box 136)
      - Memphis, 1970-1972 (Box 136, Folder 3)
      - Nashville from 1965, 1965-1970 (Box 136, Folder 4)
      - Oak Ridge, PP of Southern Mts, 1965-1972 (Box 136, Folder 5)
    - Texas
      - Austin, 1964-1970 (Box 136, Folder 6)
      - Beaumont, PP Association, 1963-1964 (Box 136, Folder 7)
      - Brownsville, PP of Cameron County, 1971 (Box 136, Folder 8)
      - Corpus Christi, 1964-1969 (Box 136, Folder 9)
      - Dallas, 1965-1970 (Box 136, Folder 10)
      - El Paso, 1965-1970 (Box 136, Folder 11)
      - Fort Worth, 1964-1974 (Box 136, Folder 12)
      - Houston, 1964-1974 (Box 136, Folder 13)
      - Lubbock, PP, 1963-1967 (Box 136, Folder 14)
      - Mission, 1964-1965 (Box 136, Folder 15)
      - Odessa, PP Permian Basin, 1972 (Box 136, Folder 16)
      - San Angelo, 1963-1964 (Box 136, Folder 17)
      - San Antonio, PP, 1960-1963 (Box 136, Folder 18)
      - Waco, 1963-1974 (Box 136, Folder 19)
    - Utah, Salt Lake City, PP, 1963-1966 (Box 136, Folder 20)
    - Vermont, Burlington, 1965 (Box 136, Folder 21)
    - Virginia, Richmond, 1963-1966 (Box 136, Folder 22)
    - Virgin Islands, St. Thomas, PP, 1964 (Box 136, Folder 23)
    - Washington
      - Seattle, 1963-1972 (Box 136, Folder 24)
      - Everett, PP Snomish County, 1972 (Box 136, Folder 25)
      - Bellingham, PP Whatcom County, 1970 (Box 136, Folder 26)
      - Yakima, 1972 (Box 136, Folder 27)
    - West Virginia, Parkersburg, 1964-1965 (Box 136, Folder 28)
    - Wisconsin, Milwaukee, 1965-1966 (Box 136, Folder 29)
    - Michigan, Great Lakes Region (formerly Mid-East), 1964-1974 (Box 136, Folder 30)
    - PPFA National: Region IV Council, 1956-1963 (Box 136, Folder 31)
    - Pennsylvania, Mid-Atlantic Region
      - 1965-1974 (Box 136, Folder 32)
      - 1975-1977 (Box 136)
    - Missouri, Midwest Region
      - 1968-1974 (Box 136, Folder 33)
      - 1975-1977 (Box 136)
    - New York
      - North Atlantic Region, 1978-1980 (Box 136, Folder 34)
      - Northeast Region, 1976-1977 (Box 136, Folder 35)
    - Texas, South Central Region, 1978 (Box 136, Folder 36)
    - Georgia, Southeast Region
      - 1964-1973 (Box 136, Folder 37)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 136)
    - Texas, Southwest Region, 1966-1973 (Box 136, Folder 38)
    - California, Western Region
      - 1965-1974 (Box 136, Folder 39)
      - 1976-1978 (Box 136)
  - PPWP Regional Councils
    - Funds Restricted to Regional Councils, 1971 (Box 136, Folder 40)
    - Regional Council Dues, 1972 (Box 136, Folder 41)
  - Great Lakes Regional Council, 1955
    - 1955-1974 (Box 136, Folder 42)
    - 1975-1977 (Box 136)
  - Ohio, Affiliates Committees from 1971 (a committee of the Council), 1971-1973 (Box 136, Folder 43)
  - Michigan PP Council, Annual Meeting, Lansing, 5/8/1973 (Box 136, Folder 44)
  - Michigan, Planned Parenthood Council from 1972 (an official committee), 1972-1974 (Box 136, Folder 45)
  - Task Force, Fourth Draft, 4/77, Function-Structure Objective, 1977 (Box 136, Folder 46)
  - Mid-Atlantic Region Council
    - 1969-1974 (Box 136, Folder 47)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 136)
  - Midwest Region Council
    - 1970-1974 (Box 136, Folder 48)
    - 1975-1977 (Box 136)
  - North Atlantic Regional Council
    - Minutes, Capital Hilton, Washington D.C., from 5/8/1980 (Box 136, Folder 49)
    - Operating Manual, 1977-1979 (Box 136, Folder 50)
    - Correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box 136, Folder 51)
    - Rules of Procedure, 1977-1978 (Box 136, Folder 52)
  - Northeast Region Council
    - 1975-1977 (Box 136, Folder 53)
    - 1970-1974 (Box 136, Folder 54)
    - Treasurer, Correspondence
      - 1977-1979 (Box 136, Folder 55)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 136, Folder 56)
  - South Central Region Council
    - 1977-1979 (Box 136, Folder 57)
    - Procedures, 1979 (Box 136, Folder 58)
    - Treasurer, Correspondence, 1978 (Box 136, Folder 59)
    - 1970-1974 (Box 136, Folder 60)
    - 1975-1977 (Box 136)
  - Southeast Regional Council: Southeast Region Council Plan, 1978 Mission, Goals, Objectives, 1978 (Box 136, Folder 61)
  - Southwest Region Council
    - 1970-1974 (Box 136, Folder 62)
    - 1975-1977 (Box 136)
    - Rules of Procedure, 1975-1977 (Box 136, Folder 63)
  - Western Region Council
    - 1970-1974 (Box 136, Folder 64)
    - 1975-1978 (Box 136)
    - Treasurer, Correspondence, 1978 (Box 136, Folder 65)
    - Rules of Procedure, 1974 (Box 136, Folder 66)
  - Regional Council, Minutes (empty) (Box 136)
  - History, Planned Parenthood Beginnings; Affiliate Histories, 1979 1979, [MISSING] (Box 136)
  - Affiliates General: Abortion Loan Fund, 1973-1974 (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - National Affiliates: Accounting Uniform
    - Correspondence, 1964-1969 (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - General, 1967 (Box 137, Folder 3)